

Phurikorn Thongyoi

062-597-6969 · phurikornpt@gmail.com · @github.com/phurikornpt 118 Soi Chan 2, Chan Road, Thung Wat Don Sathon District Bangkok 10120 web-profile: nextjs-personal-web-ten.vercel.app

PROFILE

I graduated from the Department of Electronics Engineering Technology (Computer Engineering), King Mongkut's University of Technology North Bangkok, in 2024. I gained internship experience as a Backend Developer Intern, which sparked my interest in this field. Therefore, I am interested in the position of Junior Backend Developer And I am available to start working immediately.

SKILL

- Backend
 - Javascript / Typescript
 - Node.js / Express.js
 - Nest.js
 - Firebase authentication
 - PostgreSQL / MongoDB
 - Prisma / TypeORM
 - Docker
 - Python / Go (Are learning)

Fontend

- HTML / CSS
- React / Next.js
- Mui , tailwind
- CMS
 - PayloadCMS

Tool

- Postman
- Git / Github
- · Jira, Miro
- Notion
- Languages
 - Thai (Native)
 - English (B1)

EXPERIENCE

Backend Developer Internship at Codemonday | 23 November 2023 - 31 March 2024

- Responsible for developing REST APIs and designing databases
- Developing a CMS (Content Management System) for managing content data
- Developing email templates for mail-sending systems.
- Collaborating with front-end designers, QA (Quality Assurance), and PM (Project Manager) in program development.
- · Working within Agile and Scrum frameworks.

Developed the management website for a hot pot restaurant | January 2022

- Developed a website and designed a database for internal management of the store, implementing an MVC architecture.
- Developed employee management, user permissions management, product inventory management, sales reporting, and product sales.
- Node.js/Express.js, EJS, Microsoft Access

Assisting with university research Developing AMR Robot Control Website | May 2022 - January 2023

- Developed a website to control robot operations, including creating maps, generating movement plans, and displaying real-time robot positions.
- implementing an MVC architecture in developing the website and using WebSocket to data communicate between nodejs and python in the system
- Ubuntu 18.04, Node.js/Express.js, EJS, Websocket, ROS1, Python

Assisting with university research Rice donates machine | September 2023

- Develop a website and design a database for a dashboard that displays user usage data of the Rice donates machine.
- implementing an MVC architecture in developing the website and presenting data as graphs, segmented by week, month, and year
- PHP, Mysql, Chart.js

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering Program | 2020 - 2024

Bachelor of Engineering Program in Electronics EngineeringTechnology (Computer) King Mongkut's University of Technology North Bangkok **GPAX 3.22**

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Robot Competition Event | 2022

Second Place Winner: Robot CARC Competition

Tutor | 2021 - Present

Tutor in programming:

- Python
- Arduino / Robotics